I can't believe our first hit of lights
here! MJ, come on
pretend like you're not the happiest
you've ever been in your entire
life! I can't. I knew it! Hi, my name is
Peter Parker.
You don't remember me, but we used to know
each other. Something
bad was gonna happen and the only way to
stop it was
to make everyone forget about me. Because
I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider -Man.
But you're one great. Suit yourself! Go
home! And sometimes Spider -Man
has to do the hard thing, even if it
breaks Peter Parker's
heart. What is happening to me? Oh, gosh!
Excuse me, Dr. Banner,
I need your help. What do you say,
everyone? 15A's mutating could
be enormously dangerous. Spiders have
three life cycles. When between cycles, it
can leave the spider vulnerable to
threats.
We are faced with a danger, but we can't
control. One we
can't even see. Stay out of my way. You
losing a kid?
And for those spiders who make it through,
it amounts to a
kind of... ...keeper. Nice flowers. Oh,
they're, uh, housewarming gift. I'm, uh,
MJ. I'm just a neighbor from across the
hall. It's friendly neighbor.